You're now done with the machinery learning workflow lesson.
Congrats. This is the first step on your journey to become a self-driving car engineer.
In this lesson, you learned the basic principle of the machinery workflow.
From setting up a problem to choosing the best metrics.
You learned the importance of understanding your data-sets.
Finally, you also discovered the importance of
cross-validation and how to leverage it to select machinery models.
As machinery engineers say,
a model is as good as its data and
I cannot highlight enough how important this saying is.
As a machinery engineer,
you need to cherish your data and become one with it.
In the next lesson,
we will learn more about digital images.
The type of data we will focus on in this course.